<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HamburgerTester</string>
    <string name="john_doe">John Doe</string>
    <string name="verified">Verified</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="notifactions">notifactions</string>
    <string name="profile">profile</string>

    <string name="Title"><u>Title</u></string>


    //main Strings
    <string name="aashmanDesc">Mainly focused on backend development. He created the beginning implementation for API request that where used through out the app. He is responsible for the data seen in all screens.</string>
    <string name="ST_desc">Mainly focused UI and design. He is responsible for the cartoonistic theme used throughout the app. Implemented animations, the scroll view, and fragments to make a smooth user interface. He is responsible for the UI seen in all screens</string>
    <string name="En_desc">Mainly focused on backend development.</string>


    //Mars Rover strings
    <string name="roverProgram_info">The goal of the Mars Exploration Program is to explore Mars and to provide a continuous flow of scientific information and discovery through a carefully selected series of robotic orbiters, landers and mobile laboratories interconnected by a high-bandwidth Mars/Earth communications network.</string>
     <string name="rover_info">Curiosity is a car-sized Mars rover designed to explore the Gale crater on Mars as part of NASAs Mars Science Laboratory mission. Curiosity was launched from Cape Canaveral on 26 November 2011, at 15:02:00 UTC and landed on Aeolis Palus inside Gale crater on Mars on 6 August 2012, 05:17:57 UTC.</string>
    <string name="roverTitle"><u>Mars Rover</u></string>


    //Iss strings
    <string name="issDefaultInfo">Payloads: Antioxidant Protection: Experiment Containers were installed into Kubik-5. The PROtection MEdiated by antioxidant nanoTEchnOlogy against neuronal damage in space (PROMETEO) (Antioxidant Protection) investigation proposes the use of biocompatible and biodegradable polydopamine-based nanoparticles to provide antioxidant protection to neurons undergoing exposure to altered gravity and cosmic radiation. Cellbox-3: Cellbox-3 Experiment Containers were installed into the …</string>


    //Satellite Strings
    <string name="sampleSatelliteName">Sputnik 1</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleLat">Latitude: 42.0947</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleLong">Longitude: 88.0648</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleAlt">Altitude: 741</string>
    <!-- These are the fremd coords :) -->



    //Solar System Strings
    <string name="mars_info">Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System, being larger than only Mercury. In the English language, Mars is named for the Roman god of war. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, and has a crust primarily composed of elements similar to Earth crust, as well as a core made of iron and nickel. Mars has surface features such as impact craters, valleys, dunes, and polar ice caps.</string>

</resources>