<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HamburgerTester</string>
    <string name="john_doe">John Doe</string>
    <string name="verified">Verified</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="notifactions">notifactions</string>
    <string name="profile">profile</string>

    <string name="Title"><u>Title</u></string>


    //main Strings
    <string name="aashmanDesc">Mainly focused on backend development. He created the beginning implementation for API request that where used through out the app. He is responsible for the data seen in all screens.</string>
    <string name="ST_desc">Mainly focused UI and design. He is responsible for the cartoonistic theme used throughout the app. Implemented animations, the scroll view, and fragments to make a smooth user interface. He is responsible for the UI seen in all screens</string>
    <string name="En_desc">Mainly focused on backend development. He worked on ISS and Satellites, and focused on the debugging that came with the Recycler view and APIs.</string>
    <string name="newsTitle"><u>Title</u></string>


    //Mars Rover strings
    <string name="roverProgram_info">The goal of the Mars Exploration Program is to explore Mars and to provide a continuous flow of scientific information and discovery through a carefully selected series of robotic orbiters, landers and mobile laboratories interconnected by a high-bandwidth Mars/Earth communications network.</string>
    <string name="rover_info">Curiosity is a car-sized Mars rover designed to explore the Gale crater on Mars as part of NASAs Mars Science Laboratory mission. Curiosity was launched from Cape Canaveral on 26 November 2011, at 15:02:00 UTC and landed on Aeolis Palus inside Gale crater on Mars on 6 August 2012, 05:17:57 UTC.</string>
    <string name="roverTitle"><u>Mars Rover</u></string>


    //Iss strings
    <string name="issDefaultInfo">Payloads: Antioxidant Protection: Experiment Containers were installed into Kubik-5. The PROtection MEdiated by antioxidant nanoTEchnOlogy against neuronal damage in space (PROMETEO) (Antioxidant Protection) investigation proposes the use of biocompatible and biodegradable polydopamine-based nanoparticles to provide antioxidant protection to neurons undergoing exposure to altered gravity and cosmic radiation. Cellbox-3: Cellbox-3 Experiment Containers were installed into the …</string>
    <string name="issTitle"><u>Iss Update</u></string>

    //Satellite Strings
    <string name="sampleSatelliteName">Sputnik 1</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleLat">Latitude: 42.0947</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleLong">Longitude: 88.0648</string>
    <string name="satelliteSampleAlt">Altitude: 741</string>
    <!-- These are the fremd coords :) -->


    //Solar System Strings
    // All info is from NASA's website
    <string name="mercury_info">The smallest planet in our solar system and nearest to the Sun, Mercury is only slightly larger than Earths Moon. From the surface of Mercury, the Sun would appear more than three times as large as it does when viewed from Earth, and the sunlight would be as much as seven times brighter. Despite its proximity to the Sun, Mercury is not the hottest planet in our solar system – that title belongs to nearby Venus, thanks to its dense atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="venus_info">Venus is the second planet from the Sun and is Earth’s closest planetary neighbor. It’s one of the four inner, terrestrial (or rocky) planets, and it’s often called Earth’s twin because it’s similar in size and density. These are not identical twins, however – there are radical differences between the two worlds. Venus has a thick, toxic atmosphere filled with carbon dioxide and it’s perpetually shrouded in thick, yellowish clouds of sulfuric acid that trap heat, causing a runaway greenhouse effect.</string>
    <string name="earth_info">Our home planet is the third planet from the Sun, and the only place we know of so far that’s inhabited by living things. While Earth is only the fifth largest planet in the solar system, it is the only world in our solar system with liquid water on the surface. Just slightly larger than nearby Venus, Earth is the biggest of the four planets closest to the Sun, all of which are made of rock and metal. Earths atmosphere is 78 percent nitrogen, 21 percent oxygen and 1 percent other ingredients—the perfect balance to breathe and live.</string>
    <string name="mars_info">Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun – a dusty, cold, desert world with a very thin atmosphere. Mars is also a dynamic planet with seasons, polar ice caps, canyons, extinct volcanoes, and evidence that it was even more active in the past.Mars is one of the most explored bodies in our solar system, and its the only planet where we have sent rovers to roam the alien landscape. NASA currently has two rovers, one lander, and one helicopter exploring the surface of Mars.</string>
    <string name="jupiter_info">Fifth in line from the Sun, Jupiter is, by far, the largest planet in the solar system – more than twice as massive as all the other planets combined.Jupiters familiar stripes and swirls are actually cold, windy clouds of ammonia and water, floating in an atmosphere of hydrogen and helium. Jupiter’s iconic Great Red Spot is a giant storm bigger than Earth that has raged for hundreds of years. One spacecraft – NASAs Juno orbiter – is currently exploring this giant world.</string>
    <string name="saturn_info">Saturn is the sixth planet from the Sun and the second-largest planet in our solar system. Adorned with thousands of beautiful ringlets, Saturn is unique among the planets. It is not the only planet to have rings – made of chunks of ice and rock – but none are as spectacular or as complicated as Saturns. Like fellow gas giant Jupiter, Saturn is a massive ball made mostly of hydrogen and helium. Saturns atmosphere is made up mostly of hydrogen (H2) and helium (He). </string>
    <string name="uranus_info">Uranus is the seventh planet from the Sun, and has the third-largest diameter in our solar system. It was the first planet found with the aid of a telescope, Uranus was discovered in 1781 by astronomer William Herschel, although he originally thought it was either a comet or a star. Uranus is an ice giant. Most of its mass is a hot, dense fluid of "icy" materials – water, methane and ammonia – above a small rocky core. Uranus has 13 known rings. The inner rings are narrow and dark and the outer rings are brightly colored.</string>
    <string name="neptune_info">Dark, cold, and whipped by supersonic winds, ice giant Neptune is the eighth and most distant planet in our solar system. More than 30 times as far from the Sun as Earth, Neptune is the only planet in our solar system not visible to the naked eye and the first predicted by mathematics before its discovery. In 2011 Neptune completed its first 165-year orbit since its discovery in 1846. NASAs Voyager 2 is the only spacecraft to have visited Neptune up close. It flew past in 1989 on its way out of the solar system.</string>

</resources>